{
    "subject": "resource/Clay_Davidson",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/Jude_Cole",
    "human_readable": "Clay Davidson is associated with Jude Cole.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.974867045879364,
            "question": "What is the significance of the association between Clay Davidson and Jude Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9722168445587158,
            "question": "What might be the nature of the association between Clay Davidson and Jude Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9714767932891846,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Clay Davidson and Jude Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9644421935081482,
            "question": "Are there any other individuals associated with both Clay Davidson and Jude Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9250160455703735,
            "question": "In what context are Clay Davidson and Jude Cole mentioned together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9152593016624451,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Clay Davidson's relationship with Jude Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9136295914649963,
            "question": "What do we know about the link between Clay Davidson and Jude Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8868756294250488,
            "question": "Do Clay Davidson and Jude Cole know each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8410995602607727,
            "question": "Who is Clay Davidson associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7955223321914673,
            "question": "How strong is the connection between Clay Davidson and Jude Cole based on the information available?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Clay Davidson is associated with Jude Cole.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8281_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Clay Davidson associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8281_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do Clay Davidson and Jude Cole know each other?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8281_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do we know about the link between Clay Davidson and Jude Cole?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8281_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8281_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents mentions that Jude Cole was a sponsor for Clay Davidson and had a significant role in his debut album, indicating an association between them."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Clay Davidson is associated with Jude Cole as his co-producer and songwriter, not as a partner or spouse.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information from text 2 states Jude Cole became Clay Davidson's sponsor, and co-produced his debut album. This indicates a professional association, not just an association.  Additionally, text 4 mentions Jude Cole produced a song with Clay Davidson.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information actually supports the association between Clay Davidson and Jude Cole.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information indicates that Jude Cole was Clay Davidson's sponsor and had a role in co-producing his debut album, but there is no mention of them being romantically or spouses associated.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}